Oh Light, have mercy...
I'm afraid, the Light won't help us here... What is this?
This is Locus.
Here matter acquires shape and becomes a part of the whole.
Perfectness is order. Order is wholeness.
If you disrupt Locus' wholeness, you will disrupt the harmony of the world...
No time for philosophy! We have to stop him!
You? This is pointless. You cannot break such a perfect structure.
Unless... You destroy matter! Destroy the Inferiors! Then the existence of Locus will lose its meaning.
We... I... The whole is calling for me. Don't count on my help.
We'll get along somehow...
Children of chaos... Why did you come to my world? I am the Architect! I am the Order!
You are going to ascend. Become perfect. Become whole... as well as our loose shard!